
[
  {
    "front": "The Embargo Act, which prohibited all foreign trade was enacted in what year?",
    "back": "1807",
    "cardType": "basic"
  },

  {
    "front": "This U.S. President was the only one to serve two non-consecutive terms in office.",
    "back": "Grover Cleveland",
    "cardType": "basic"
  },

  {
    "front": "The surprise Japanese attack on Pearl Harbor occurred on what date?",
    "back": "December 7, 1941",
    "cardType": "basic"
  },

  {
    "front": "On March 11, 1941, the Lend-Lease Act was enacted to provide food, oil, and material to Allied Nations between what years (inclusive)?",
    "back": "1941 and 1945",
    "cardType": "basic"
  },

  {
    "front": "The first Hot Wheels cars were released in what year?",
    "back": "1968",
    "cardType": "basic"
 },

  {
    "front": "what is the name of the Scorpions album released prior to Blackout?",
    "back": "Animal Magnetism",
    "cardType": "basic"
  },

  {
    "front": "According to Wikipedia, which Black Sabbath song has been covered by at least 23 well-known bands, including the Dickies?",
    "back": "Paranoid",
    "cardType": "basic"
  },

  {
    "front": "The Rush-Bagot Treaty of 1818 was a treaty limiting naval armaments on the Great Lakes and Lake Champlain following the War of 1812. Besides the United States, which other country was a signatory to this treaty?",
    "back": "Britain",
    "cardType": "basic"
  },

  {
    "front": "Before Whitey came and screwed everything up, the Seattle area was inhabited by Native Americans for at least how many years?",
    "back": "4000",
    "cardType": "basic"
  },

  {
    "front": "Of the 90 members of the Donner Party, how many were at least partially eaten.",
    "back": "52 (Everyone that died.)",
    "cardType": "basic"
  }
]